

# CONTENT CREATOR& WEB DEVELOPER.

Over 4 years of experience in Photography & Videography + 9 years of experience working with Adobe Cloud especially photoshop. Seeking to craft memorable images. Shot the picture for Belgium national day. Don't hesitate to check it out on @Ahmad\_Hendi\_.

I am able to create solid Web App using JavaScript, HTML/CSS, React and WordPress with an artistic eyes.

# Work Experience

Front End Developer Yellow Brussels (Mar 2021 - Jun 2021) I worked on different projects in which I used React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS and WordPress.

Photographer & Videographer (since 2046)
Several individual projects + collaboration with known companies (Visitbrussels, Stip Welovebrussels, The Hotel, and Bxl\_online).
I have been contacted by the mayor of Saint Josse for a collaboration.

Seller (Jun 2017 - Dec 2018)

Volunteer Asmae (Jan 2016 - Jun 2017) An organisation for multicultural projects.

(EO of Fashion4you (Feb 2013 - Aug 2015) Founder of Fashion4you accessory brand. Sold over 500 bracelets

Web Designer
(Mar 2012 - Apr 2012)
Developed and designed
informational material to
promote the
organization global reach

# Education

Full Stack Developer (Sep 2020 - Jun 2021) BeCode, Website Creation, e-commerce platform, weather app,

movie streaming, etc.

Accounting EPHEC (2019 -- 2020)

Les Mangeurs D'étoiles (Sep 2017 - Aug 2017) Editing, photography, Web design, illustration and retouching.

Economy Solvay (2016 -- 2017) Tishreen (2012 -- 2015)

#### Hard Skills

Photoshop, AfterEffect, Final Cut Pro, Premier Pro, Html, Css, JavaScript, WordPress, React.

## Soft Skills

Creativity, Flexible, Good communication, Positive attitude, Open minded.

## Portfolio



## Languages

Arabic -- Native

French -- fluent

English -- fluent

Dutch -- basic

Super motivated to learn Dutch